<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Tony Mead's Blog</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Tony Mead's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book Review - Mistborn</title><link>https://example.com/br-mistborn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-mistborn/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Book Review - Project Hail Mary</title><link>https://example.com/br-french-quarter/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-french-quarter/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Book Review - Project Hail Mary</title><link>https://example.com/br-gardens-of-the-moon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-gardens-of-the-moon/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Book Review - Project Hail Mary</title><link>https://example.com/br-project-hail-mary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-project-hail-mary/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Book Review - Project Hail Mary</title><link>https://example.com/br-red-rising/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-red-rising/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Intro MMT</title><link>https://example.com/intro-mmt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/intro-mmt/</guid><description>In regards to running a surplus and clearing out the national deficit, Clinton&amp;rsquo;s team suggested that:
What worried policy makers the most was the prospect of depriving the Federal Reserve of the key instrument it relied on to conduct monetary policy - government debt. At the time, the Fed was relying on government bonds to manage the short-term interest rate. When the Fed wanted to raise interest rates, it sold some of its Treasuries.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Theodore Rex</title><link>https://example.com/br-theodore-rex/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-theodore-rex/</guid><description>Author: Edmund Morris
Theodore was the original hustler, TGIM, and work hard play hard characture. He&amp;rsquo;s all energy and spirit, something that Morris has conveyed well in his writing because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t put that book down. On one page Theodore writes into his diary that we has a desire and on the next page, sometimes even the next paragraph, he ventures out with annoyingly predictable success at achieving it. It&amp;rsquo;s incredibly difficult not to fall in love with him, or in my case, ddeply envy him.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Mission to Mars</title><link>https://example.com/br-packing-for-mars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-packing-for-mars/</guid><description>Author: Mary Roach
This was a deeply insightful collection of newspaper style articles that revealed some disgustingly informative insight to space travel. The downside being that I had to second guess a lot of my desire to ever leave our atmosphere.
While I live out of a trailer I can echo the realities of isolation that grows when you don&amp;rsquo;t have any external outlets. Roach points out how astronaughts often blame mission control which I can empathize with as normally when the tensions rise between Lauren and I we spend hours complaining about the truck or the trailer.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Capital</title><link>https://example.com/br-capital/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-capital/</guid><description>Author: Thomas Pikkety
There&amp;rsquo;s a lot to say about a 600 page history of monies, wages, and economic policy over the last 300 years.
In fact, one of my biggest gripes with the book was the verbosity. There were several times where Pikkety repeated himself on the value of data for making informed policy decisions. Or how important democratic discussion is for setting the ideal tax rate. Packaging these ideas into a succinct concept like he does with the formulas, like r&amp;gt;g for example, was a missed opportunity to make the book more approachable to the citizenry he&amp;rsquo;s trying to equip.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Masters of Doom</title><link>https://example.com/br-masters-of-doom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-masters-of-doom/</guid><description>Author: David Kushner
I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel like some people failled Romero. With a financial and entrepenurial mentor i&amp;rsquo;m sure Romero would be in some other C-suite like Carmack.
Even though the book starts out as painting both Johns as coming from the same broken households, it&amp;rsquo;s clear by the time they split Carmack is a force of his own.
Romero has the gift of design and vision, but not to the level that some people can claim a whole career of success.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Blood and Thunder</title><link>https://example.com/br-blood-and-thunder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-blood-and-thunder/</guid><description>Author: Hampton Sides
Sides does a fantastic job weaving together the collision of culture that occured between Americans, Mexicans, and the indigenious peoples. With history often feeling one-sided here the author offers the leader a lot of room to make their own judgements. For example, when warring tribes, and even the hero Kit Carson, enslave each other children it&amp;rsquo;s discussed as &amp;ldquo;something that&amp;rsquo;s always been done&amp;rdquo;. Take this passage that highlights the difference between &amp;ldquo;chattel&amp;rdquo; and I guess the other-kind?</description></item><item><title>Book Review - The Rise of Theodore Roosevelt</title><link>https://example.com/br-the-rise-of-theodore-roosevelt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-the-rise-of-theodore-roosevelt/</guid><description>Author: Edmun Morris
This was my first autobiography so it caught me off guard at how much entrigue could be built up for one real person&amp;rsquo;s life. Reading about the death of Alice and his mother was comparable to a season finale. It took me another 100 page bing to fall asleep and by that point I was captivated by the moves with Edith. A true testiment to the writing of Morris.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Mission To Mars</title><link>https://example.com/br-mission-to-mars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-mission-to-mars/</guid><description>After reading An Astronaughts Guide to Life on Earth I have been curious about books on highly successful people. Chris&amp;rsquo;s dedication to continuously pursuing his dream was an new and exciting feeling. Yet in the the end he recognizes that many others never accomplish what they set out for and one needs to be mentally ready for that realization. With that said I was hoping for another exploration of Buzz&amp;rsquo;s life, but what I got was a primer on space policy.</description></item><item><title>Book Review - Change Agent</title><link>https://example.com/br-change-agent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/br-change-agent/</guid><description>Author: Daniel Suarez
Suarez always does his homework, the book is filled with what feels like a deep dive into biology and CRISPR. What I enjoy even better is that Suarez is clearly an engineer who always teeters on explaining too much and keeping it high level. At one point the characters debate wether to just fly strait into Marcus&amp;rsquo;s hideout, and its pointed out that there are autonomous cannons from a previous conflict still active in field.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>A collection of writings, or more likely streams of consciousness, that I need to get out of my head before I can sleep through the night.</description></item></channel></rss>